Merry Christmas!
Good morning.
Congratulations!
We wish you a very Happy Holiday season!
Please subscribe to our channel!
So this time, we're going to have a
YouTube Christmas Special!
What the hell?
What is it?
Well, you know what?
The sound of the bell is getting closer.
Is it ringing already? It's going public right now.
Isn't it ringing right now?
Chant, chant, chant, chant, chant, chant.
It's playing.
Speaking of Christmas...
What do you think, Mr. Moku?
Oh...
That's why...
I got a reindeer.
Oh!
That's good.
It's a project.
First things first.
You start here.
We'll go to the snow country.
You'll get a real reindeer.
You'll be the first to get a real reindeer.
Sunny Bran!
Okay, how about the rest of you?
How about you, Mr. Ryoto?
You guessed it, right?
Yes, sir.
Uh...
Um...
Well, speaking of Santa...
Santa Claus.
Santa Claus
Santa Claus wears a red suit, right?
That's why the red Santa Claus outfit
Santa Claus
Oh, Santa Claus.
Ha-ha-ha.
Red Santa Claus code.
Santa Claus.
You mean you're going to dress up as Santa Claus?
Yes, I do.
Then we'll get it next year.
We'll get it next year.
What do you think? Mr. Tomasol.
But calm down.
I went to the Red Brick Warehouse in Yokohama.
I went there.
I tried.
Oh, no.
Why? It's a little weird.
I tried.
You're right, you're right.
Okay, Mr. Kousaku.
Hey...
I knew it!
What is it? That, right?
The gift exchange.
Oh!
Oh, yeah!
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's great, that's great, that's great.
That's right.
This time.
Yes, yes, yes.
To all of you, everyone.
I'd like to do a Christmas-only gift exchange.
Yay!
Last year, you know, we did it on insta-live.
You did it, you did it.
We did it!
We did it.
Today, we're going to do it on YouTube.
Yes, this time we are going to do it on YouTube.
I'd like to give each of you a little gift in advance.
I have a little present for each of you.
Wow!
I may have prepared a little gift for you.
I did.
Please, have a seat.
What do you think? How much?
How much thought went into your choice?
Oh, my God, so much sincerity.
Sincerity!
I see. Really.
Well, you know, something that anyone would be happy to receive...
I don't know, last year
I had the image that everyone was pretty out of it.
That's for sure.
And I thought, "I don't need any more blurbs.
That's true.
So..,
Knock, knock.
Got it.
I thought, "I don't need any more bokeh.
And I thought, "No one's going to be blabbing anymore this year.
I was serious about my choice.
I'm the same way.
So, here we are.
So, how are we going to do the gift exchange this time?
I was wondering if you'd like to do this on insta-live?
That's nice.
That's how it was.
This time, first of all
Oh, oh, oh?
We're going to announce the contents of the gift in advance.
Oh, so that's how it's going to be.
On the contrary?
What?
So?
This time, we'd like you to announce the contents of your gift.
And why you chose it.
Yeah.
We'd like you to present the appeal points first.
However...
I have your presents here...
Yes.
We still don't know who they belong to.
What?
You mean you're giving them away without saying which bag they're from?
That's right.
I see.
I'm the one who bought this bag, not this one, but the one I bought.
After you explain it once...
Well, I really want a bag of canary beans.
Which bag do you put the canary in?
What size is it? I'll ask you to imagine.
So that's what you're saying.
That's why you told me not to wrap it at the store.
I see.
And then, as soon as we're done, we play rock-paper-scissors to choose one person at a time to open the package.
Rock-paper-scissors.
It's complicated.
Yes, it is.
It's difficult.
So it's possible that one person will be popular with six people and no one else.
It's possible.
Is there a possibility that you won't get this one?
No, it's not.
Is there any chance that you won't get it?
No.
No?
Who wouldn't get it at a gift exchange, right?
No.
It's possible if, for example, the craftsman didn't prepare it.
Yeah.
Maybe...
Maybe.
There are seven of them.
I don't know.
Well then, let's see if we can announce them one by one.
Here we go.
The one I bought is...
There it is.
It's a phone shield.
Oh, my goodness!
You've got a great lineup.
Very nice.
I thought there was a limit to how much you could charge.
If we had to pick one of them...
I wondered who would be happy to win.
Then I thought about what everyone does in common.
I thought about dancing and singing.
Singing...
There were a lot of things.
Everyone has a smartphone, right?
I thought, "Well, everyone has a smartphone.
I bought it because
It can hold a smartphone and a tablet.
Wow!
I was thinking that some of our members have tablets.
That's for sure.
Like when you're eating a meal.
I put it on the desk.
I put it on the table like this.
You can watch it while sitting down.
I bought something that I can watch while sitting down.
No, that's really good.
I think you should sell it.
I think you should sell it on YouTube or something.
Now it's a special offer!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's like, "No, it's not.
I'll have you guys announce it.
I'll just announce it here.
I want one of these.
But I don't know which bag it's in.
I don't know which bag it's in.
Well, let's go, Mr. Jun.
I'm a little close to Takatoro myself.
I'm close to Takatoro.
I'd like to have one, but I'd be happy to take it.
It's an extension.
Oh!
Hold on.
Get it.
I want it, I want it, I want it, seriously.
Wait a minute.
I want it, I want it, I want it, I want it.
There's a genius.
The more extended action, the better.
The more extended action you have, the less trouble you'll have.
It's a no-brainer.
That's right.
Electronics.
Chargers.
All at once.
Smartphones and
AirPods
earphones, etc.
When you want to charge your phone and AirPods at the same time
I'm in the field, and there's an outlet too far away.
I really want one.
Sometimes I have to stand up to get there.
Sometimes you can't.
Sometimes you can't even sit down when you plug in.
That's why you should do that.
I'd be really happy to get it.
It's a little less of a bad thing.
I really want it!
I've been seriously thinking about it.
Gentlemen!
In 2023...
Don't you see many members dyed their hair?
Yes, for sure.
I also dyed my hair brown.
I dyed my hair brown.
I did a lot of things.
Like a tiger.
Iger.
And I did a lot of other things.
You did a lot of haircuts, didn't you?
My hair.
It's damaged.
Oh!
It's so damaged.
But! But!
I'm sure everyone has hair oil or something.
I'm sure everyone has hair oil, and without it, it's impossible.
What I prepared this time is...
A high quality comb!
Wow!
Seriously?
I need a good melt.
Wow, I want it!
While I heal in the future.
I want it so bad.
I see what you mean.
If you sleep with it melted down...
I'm sure you'll end up with less of a sleeping habit.
Oh, wow!
Plus, it won't damage your hair.
I see.
That's why I prepared the comb.
Oh, that's nice.
I want one.
I want it, I want it, I want it.
I want it. I want it.
I want it.
Oh, that's nice.
Gentlemen.
Hey!
I thought you were all very tired this year.
Yes, I am.
I knew it.
What's so hard on your shoulders?
Bath time...
I think it's important.
A bathtub...
Or taking a bath...
No, but...
No, it's not.
Well, I think that's where they'll be using their phones.
That's where I was thinking...
Music is important.
Yes, yes, yes.
Speakers that can be used in the bath
Oh!
Great.
That's great.
Oh, man.
I thought you all might be surprised that I don't have it.
You're right, you're right.
Surprisingly, there are no speakers for the bathtub.
I didn't know there was such a thing.
I want one.
By the way, how many of you take care of your bathtubs?
There are a lot of them.
Well, this is it.
Then, do any of you take a bath in this bathtub too?
Yes, they do.
Twice a day.
No, I don't.
So that means...
Almost.
That's nice.
No, I want one.
Yes, I want it.
So, how was it, Mr. Kosaku?
Ah, yes, everyone.
Gentlemen.
Like the host.
Maybe he's a dark horse.
I'm sure.
It's been a year.
I'm sure there are a lot of tired people out there.
It's a little while away.
That's why.
Of all the people out there.
I've prepared this for you.
Oh.
Hot eye mask.
Oh!
Oh, that's good.
That's so good.
I want one.
I'm done with this.
For now.
Oh, hey.
It's nice.
But we have tools.
Great. Three of us.
Wait a minute.
What?
Huh?
That's...
What kind of hot eye mask?
I don't know.
I don't know yet.
It's...
It's just...
Yu-kun, that thing that everyone uses...
Steam
use-it-up
Steam hot eye mask
use up
I see.
You cut corners.
No, no, no.
No, I'm glad.
I want one.
Like a par-tour.
I mean, you can consume this stuff.
Oh, on the contrary.
Yeah, on the contrary.
I mean, it's like...
It's not an ornament.
That's for sure.
It's not bulky.
I see.
You know...
You're wearing perfume these days.
Yes, yes, yes.
And I think you pay a lot of attention to the scent of fragrances when you go outside.
I think you pay a lot of attention to what you smell when you go outside.
You have grown up, haven't you?
You've grown up, haven't you?
The smell inside the house...
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the 75th birthday present.
You care about it.
You do care.
Thank you for what?
But I think you probably have a diffuser.
I think you probably have a diffuser in the room.
Oh, a diffuser.
No, no...
But I'd like to recommend...
Incense.
Raoul-oh.
Uxalau сделал
Raoul life
And incense
People think it's expensive.
I've heard of it.
It's surprisingly easy to put on
And it instantly creates a relaxing atmosphere.
Incense
Don't you think it's good?
No, no, no, it's very good.
By the way, incense...
Not a set of incense burners.
Incense?
No?
Just incense? But incense...
If you put a plate on it, it'll be fine.
Oh, yes.
Incense alone.
There's definitely at least one heatproof plate.
If you want to make a gratin or something...
Incense?
You're talking about a plate?
Maybe...
Maybe it comes with an incense burner.
That's why I have incense.
I'm so happy, I'm so happy.
Oh, my God.
It's quality.
I thought it was quality or feeling.
I'm giving it to this member.
I want something that makes you happy.
I thought it should be something with a lot of feeling.
Something handmade.
Seriously, handmade.
Seriously, stop with the homemade stuff.
I worked hard all night.
Good handmade.
Seriously?
Collage I made myself
Photo frame
It comes with a set of my purikura!
I've heard that one before.
I heard that's what you did last time.
Last time I was alone.
I went and took purikura pictures.
I decorated it and gave it to her.
And then...
I thought that if I gave it to a crafts person...
I wanted to give it to him.
How many minutes did you make?
That's already two.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
If we keep this up, it'll last six more years.
Six more years.
Didn't we decide not to do chokers this year?
I did.
I'm not being choke-happy.
It's just how I feel.
Nerves.
How long does it take you to make a film?
Night after night.
We've been seeing each other every day lately.
It's more than every day, isn't it?
I go out first thing in the morning to shoot.
To shoot? Yeah, we're filming, right?
To buy stuff.
I bought a lot of stuff.
It takes about an hour to make it, including the night work.
It took me about two hours.
About two hours?
A couple of hours?
And it's not finished yet.
You haven't finished it?
When you decide to give it to someone...
I'll do this to that person.
Desperation.
Seriously?
That's why it's done.
A phone stand?
Yes, a phone stand.
Speakers.
Eye mask?
Skewer.
Homemade.
Purikura photo frame.
Oh, no.
I want one.
How did you do that?
As for the picture frame.
We have a self-contained room.
It's called a purikura, and it's for the fans.
Yeah, there's only one for each of the four of us.
You mean the little ones?
But I got one and it made me pretty happy.
By the way, now...
If you do it now, it's probably between the two books.
Oh...
That's the best.
If it's vertical, it's still there, but it's sideways.
I haven't read the horizontal book
I'd like to actually
I'd like to actually choose a gift from here.
I'd like to actually pick out a present from here.
Ready, set, go!
First, let's play rock-paper-scissors-paper.
I'm so happy to see so many presents
But... all that's left is fine.
I did it because I worked so hard